{
"question": "此処",
"answer": "ここ"
},
{
"question": "前",
"answer": "まえ"
},
{
"question": "もう",
"answer": "もう"
},
{
"question": "如何",
"answer": "どう"
},
{
"question": "方",
"answer": "かた"
},
{
"question": "未だ",
"answer": "まだ"
},
{
"question": "もっと",
"answer": "もっと"
},
{
"question": "何時",
"answer": "いつ"
},
{
"question": "パーティ",
"answer": "パーティー"
},
{
"question": "他",
"answer": "ほか"
},
{
"question": "次",
"answer": "つぎ"
},
{
"question": "ドア",
"answer": "ドア"
},
{
"question": "何方",
"answer": "どちら"
},
{
"question": "誰か",
"answer": "だれか"
},
{
"question": "開く-1",
"answer": "あく"
},
{
"question": "どうぞ",
"answer": "どうぞ"
},
{
"question": "こんな",
"answer": "こんな"
},
{
"question": "下",
"answer": "した"
},
{
"question": "然して",
"answer": "そして"
},
{
"question": "ゆっくり",
"answer": "ゆっくり"
},
